Guide to the Love Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Love family papers
1872-1958
MS 12
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.5
(5 boxes)
Correspondence, printed materials, theater programs, photographs and other papers of Lucy Cleveland Prindle Love and Helen Douglas Love Scranton, wife and daughter, respectively, of Edward Gurley Love and active in New York social and cultural life in the early 20th century.The correspondence is chiefly from theatrical personalities and writers and concerns cultural life in New York City. Prominent among the correspondents are Pearl S. Buck, Andrew Carnegie, Thomas Alva Edison, Clara Clemens, Helen Keller, Kate Douglas Wiggin Riggs, Jules Verne and Alexander Woollcott.
Love family
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the estate of Helen Douglas Love Scranton, l969.
Arrangement
I. Correspondence. II. Miscellaneous. III. Printed Materials. IV. Photographs.
Scope and Contents
The Love Family Papers consist primarily of letters to Lucy Cleveland Prindle Love (Mrs. Edward Gurley Love) and a lesser amount to her daughter, Helen Douglas (Love) Scranton, written during the early and middle years of the twentieth century. Many of the letters are from theatrical personalities and authors as Dame Sybil Thorndike, Kate Douglas Wiggin and Ben Greet (Sir Philip Ben Greet, 1857-1936), and comment on various cultural activities in New York City and America. Mrs. Love was the wife of Edward Gurley Love, a chemical engineer who held a Ph.D. from Columbia University. A graduate of Hamilton College (1822), he received the Ph.B. from Columbia in 1876 and the Ph.D. in 1876. In 1877, he was appointed to the newly created post of gas examiner for New York City. During World War I, Mr. Love worked for the U.S. Government and constructed a large plant for the recovery of toluol from the gas used for city lighting, the product being used for the manufacture of TNT.
The Loves lived on the East Side of Manhattan and their interest in the arts is evident in this collection of Mrs. Love's correspondence, much of which concerns a production of PARSIFAL given in 1904 which she supported. Her daughter, Helen, was Secretary of the Society of the Friends of Music and most of her correspondence is related to the placing of subscriptions by prominent social personalities of the day such as William Lyon Phelps. Helen (Love) Scranton was the second wife of William Dowd Scranton, an 1897 graduate of Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, and later lived in Madison, Connecticut. Historically, the papers would be of greatest interest to the student of theater history. The Ben Greet correspondence is the largest file in the collection and at one time Mrs. Scranton considered writing a biography based in part on these papers. These papers would also furnish source material for the social historian interested in the development of New York City as a leading cultural center of the world during the early part of this century. The Love Family Papers were left to the Yale University Library by the estate of Helen (Love) Scranton in 1969.
Separated Materials
Autograph letters removed from Lulu C. Prindle autograph album and dispersed among Manuscripts and Archives collections:
Botta, Anne Charlotte (Lynch) 1815-1891 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Brace, Charles Loring 1826-1890 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Britten, Harriet G. [?] (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Brooks, Phillips 1835-1893 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Cash, James l839-1909 [?] (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Chandler, Charles Frederick 1836-1925 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Cleveland, Grover, Pres. U.S. 1837-1908 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Conkling, Roscoe 1829-1888 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Cooper, James Fenimore 1789-1851 (Morse Family Papers - MS 358)
Curtis, George William 1824-1892
Custman, Charlotte [?] (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Dana, James Dwight 1813-1895 (Dana Family Papers - MS 164)
Fay, Theodore Sedgewick 1807-1898 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Garrison, William Lloyd 1805-1879 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Godwin, Parke 1816-1904 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Guyot, Arnold Henry 1807-1884 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Harte, Bret 1836-1902 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Hayne, Robert Young 1791-1839 (Morse Family Papers - MS 358)
Hicks, Thomas 1823-1890 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Hillard, George Stillman 1808-1879 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Holmes, Oliver Wendell 1809-1884 (Misc. Mss-2 letters - MS 352)
Ingelow, Jean 1820-1897 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Kimball, Richard Burleigh 1816-1892 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Kirkland, Caroline Matilda (Stansbury) 1801-1864 ( Misc. Mss)
Lanman, Charles 1819-1895 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth 1807-1882 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
MacDonald, George 1824-1905 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Mehloef, Anna [?] ( Misc. Mss)
Morse, Samuel Finley Breese 1791-1872 (Morse Family Papers - MS 358)
Phelps, Elizabeth Stuart 1844-1911 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Porter, Samuel 1810-1901 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Porter, Sarah 1813-1900 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Sands, Henry Berton 1830-1888 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Seebach, Marie (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Sheriden, Philip Henry 1831-1888 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Silliman, Benjamin 1816-1885 (Silliman Family Papers - MS 450)
Taylor, Bayard 1825-1878 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Terhune, Mary Virginia Hawes 1830-1922 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
Tupper, Martin Farquhar 1810-1889 (Morse Family Papers - MS 358)
Wilson, Augusta Jane (Evans) 1835-1909 (Miscellaneous Manuscript Collection - MS 352)
(plus 4 unidentified letters in Misc. Mss folder "Unidentified")
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Families; Music; Theater -- New York (State) -- New York -- History; Theater; New York (N.Y.) -- Social life and customs; New York (State); Photoprints; Buck, Pearl S. (Pearl Sydenstricker), 1892-1973; Carnegie, Andrew, 1835-1919; Clemens, Clara, 1874-1962; Dodge, Mary Mapes, 1830-1905; Edison, Thomas A. (Thomas Alva), 1847-1931; Garland, Hamlin, 1860-1940; Gray, Asa, 1810-1888; Greet, Ben, Sir, 1857-1936; Grenfell, Wilfred Thomason, Sir, 1865-1940; Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1823-1911; Howells, William Dean, 1837-1920; La Farge, John, 1835-1910; Love, Lucy Cleveland Prindle; Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943; Porter, Noah, 1811-1892; Reid, Whitelaw, 1837-1912; Scranton, Helen D. Love (Helen Douglas Love), 1879-1968; Thorndike, Sybil, Dame, 1882-1976; Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1872-1949; Wiggin, Kate Douglas Smith, 1856-1923; Woollcott, Alexander, 1887-1943; Yurka, Blanche; Love family
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1880-1958; Series I; 15" 3 Boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence is arranged in alphabetical order by last name of the sender or recipient. Within each folder, the letters are then placed in chronological order.
  People included in the correspondence are: Pearl S. Buck, Andrew Carnegie, Thomas Alva Edison, Clara (Clemens) Babrilowilsch, Hamlin Garland, Herbert Hoover, Helen Keller, Kate Douglas (Wiggin) Riggs, Jules Verne, A.H. Woolcott and many other noted people.
  Unidentified material is grouped together in a folder found alphabetically under U, and is in chronological order with undated material at the end.
  - Abbott, A.F.H., 1899 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Lyman, 1904-1907 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adler, Felix, 1895-1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Dallas, 1903-1916, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anthony, Katharine, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Austand, Brancis, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bacon, Josephine O., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Baird, W. W., 1885 (Box 1, Folder 7a)
  - Barker, Fordyce, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Barry, John Kendrick, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baruch, E., 1903-1907 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Baucroft, Cecil F.P., 1900 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bauer, Harold, 1905-1928 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Beame, Austin, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Beard, W. H., undated (Box 1, Folder 13a)
  - Beckwith, Carroll, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 13b)
  - Beind, Eric, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bement, Alan, 1905-1907, n.d (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bement, William, 1907-1912, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bigelow, Poultney, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bitter, Karl, 1908, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Blashfield, E. H, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 18a)
  - Bliss, C.N., 1907 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bloch, Albert, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 19a)
  - Blow, Susan, 1909-1912 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bratwall, G.C.F., 1914 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brewer, Victor, 1910-1911 (Box 1, Folder 21a)
  - Brownell, W.C., 1901 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Buck, Pearl, S., 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1904-1910 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Butter, Howard, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Carnegie, Andrew, 1896-1901 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cemola, L. P., 1883 (Box 1, Folder 26a)
  - Chandler, C.F., 1896 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chapin, Anna Alice, 1898-1899 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Chapin, Elsie, 1899-1904 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Chapman, John Joy, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Christy, Howard C., 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder 30a)
  - Church, H., undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - City Club of New York, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Clarke, Sir Purdon, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Cleveland, Frances F., 1894 (Box 1, Folder 33a)
  - Colfax, Schuyler, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 33b)
  - Comstock, Ann Botsford, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Cortlow, Henry N., 1879 (Box 1, Folder 34a)
  - Cortelyou, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Craigie, Pearl Mary, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Curtis, J.G., 1899 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Custer, Mrs. Elizabeth Bacon, 1896-1933 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Daly, Arnold, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Daskam, Josephine, 1903, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Davies, Arthur, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Davis, Jonathan, 1895-1898 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Davis, Richard Harding, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - De Cordova, R., 1910 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Dein, Herman, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Dodge, Mary Mapes, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Dodge, W.E., 1899 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Dole, Nathan Haskell, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Duly, J.F., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Dwight, Theodore W., 1884 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Eastman, Elaine G., undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Edison, Thomas Alva, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Ely, Robert E., undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Faversham, Julia Opp, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Field, Ben A., 1904-1905 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Fitch, Clyde, n.d (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Forbes-Robertson, M., 1909 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Ford, Willis, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Fox, C.C., 1890 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Frohman, Daniel, 1899-1902 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Fromkes, Maurice, 1906-1919, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Fry, Horace B., 1903-1905 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Gabrilowilsch, Clara (Clemens), 1918 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Gallwey, W.B.W., 1899 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Garland, Hamlin, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Ghosh, Sarath, 1915-1917 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Gilder, R.W., 1896-1905 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Grant, Percy S., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Gray, Asa, undated (Box 2, Folder 68a)
  - Genet, Sir Philip Ben, 1896-1906 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Greet, Ben, 1907-1932 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Grenfell, Wilfred T., 1929 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Grimm, Leighton, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Gurnett, Frances Hodgeon, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Hapsford, Anthony F., 1900-1909 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Hawkins, Anthony H., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Hawthorne, Julian, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Hervey, Wlater S., 1897, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Hinton, Katharine (Goodson), 1914 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Holt, H., 1916 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Hoover, Herbert (form letter of appeal), 1946 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Horsford, E. W., 1883 (Box 2, Folder 81a)
  - Howard, L.O., 1893-1898 (Box 2, Folder 82-83)
  - Hughes, James L., 1903-1906 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Hunter, Jenny, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Irwin, Beatrice, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Jameson, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Japper, Thomas, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Johnson, Helen K., 1895-1902 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Johnson, Rossiter, 1903-1916 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Keith, Donald, August 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 90a)
  - Keller, Helen (form letter), 1943 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Kelly, Meyra, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Kennedy, C. Rann, 1904-1908 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Kennedy, Edith Wynne, 1902-1935 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Keppler, Rudolph, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Knapp, H., 1895-1898 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Kneisel, Franz, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Knobbe, Gustav, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Kraus-Bosilto, Emma & Maria, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Lafarge, John, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 99a)
  - Lanier, Mary (Day), 1918 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Leiber, Fritz, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Loeb, Louis, 1908, undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Long, John. D, 1880 (Box 3, Folder 102a)
  - Longfellow, Ernest W., 1920 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Low, Seth, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Mabie, H.W., 1894-1905 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - McLaughlin, Millicent, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Magnisson, Sigrid W., 1897 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Mahan, Alfred Thayer, undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Manley, Thomas R., 1891-1910 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Manning, William T., 1925 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Mansfield, Richard, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Marlowe, Julia, undated (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Marquand, Abram, 1910-1911 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Matthews, Brander, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Maynard, Richard F., 1903, 1917, 1936, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Moody, D.L., 1889 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Nies, Konrad, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Nisbet, R.J., 1920 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Oratorio Society, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Osborne, Thomas M., 1907-1914 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Palmer, Ray, 1882 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Parker, Gilbert, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Phelps, Austin, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Phelps, Elizabeth Stuart, 1880 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Porter, Noah, 1883 (Box 3, Folder 125a)
  - Potter, H. C., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Prime, W.C., 1898 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Pryer, Charles, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Rees, Alys, 1904-1911 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1875 (Box 3, Folder 129a)
  - Riggs, Kate Douglas (Wiggin), 1894, 1896-1909, undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Riley, C.V., 1892-1894 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Rittenhouse, Jessie B., undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Schauffler, Rovert Haven, 1915-1916 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Scollard, Jessie Rittenhouse, 1924-1925, undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Sedgwick, H.D., undated (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Seligman, Edwin K., 1899-1907 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Shipman, Hubert, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Sikes, Olive Logan, undated (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Stryker, Dr., n.d (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Stuart, Ruth, M., undated (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Sturney, Charles M., undated (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Sutphen, Van Tassel, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Terhune, Mary Virginia, 1884 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Thomas, Augustine, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Thorndike, Russel, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Thorndike, Dame Sybil, 1904-1957 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Upjohn, Berthe, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Unidentified, 1880-1919, undated (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Van Dyke, Henry, 1899, undated (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Van Dyke, John C., 1906 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Van Dyke, William, 1905-1910 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Veiller, Bayard, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Villard, Fanny G., 1905 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Villard, Oswald, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Vivian, Violet, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Von Bulow, Baroness, 1897-1900 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Wakerman, Keith, undated (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Wald, Lillian D., 1913, undated (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - S.H. Wales & Son, undated (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Waram, Percy, undated (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Warner, Susan, 1873-1885,undated (Box 3, Folder 160a)
  - Waterbaumb, F., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 160b)
  - Wendell, Evert Jansen, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Wilson, C., 1904 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Woolcott, A.H., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Wyckerly, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Wyckoff, Wallin A., 1898 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Yurka, Blanche, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Unidentified, 1873, undated (Box 3, Folder 166)
- MISCELLANEOUS, 1872, 1913- 1914; Series II; 2" 1/3 Box
  Included in this series are an essay entitled "Dictations on Art" by Lulu C. Love, checks, receipts from the Kneisel Quartet, sketches and autographs of William Dean Howells, Jules Verne, Ben Greet and others.
  - Lulu C. (Prindle) Love, "Dictations on Art", 1872 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Checks, undated (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Kneisel Quartet, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Autographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 171)
- PRINTED MATERIALS, 1874-1936; Series III; 2" 1/3 Box
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by name of subject or type of material with miscellaneous and unidentified material at the end. Included are a pictorial souvenir of Maude Adams in "L'Aiglon", publicity material for Harold Bauer, Ben Greet, Mr. & Mrs. Charles Hopkins and Vivien George, theater programs, and wedding and burial announcements.
  - Adams, Maude as "L'Aiglon", 1901 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Bauer, Harold, 1915-1924, undated (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Greet, Ben, 1911-1936 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Hopkines, Mr. & Mrs. Charles, undated (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - "Little Lord Fauntleroy", undated (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Theater Programs, 1874-1936 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Vivien, George, undated (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Wedding & Burial Announcements, 1899, 1910, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Miscellaneous, 1886-1913 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 4, Folder 181)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1897-1898, 1903-1904,1908-1909, 1929; Series IV; 8" 1 1/3 Boxes
  Photographs are arranged in alphabetical order by the subjects' last names. Unidentified photos are at the end of the series.
  These photos consist of individuals such as Harold Bauer, Ben Greet, Kate Douglas (Wiggin) Riggs, and others who figure prominently in collection.
  - Alesandier, Adelaide, undated (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Anderson, Dallas, undated (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Bauer, Harold, undated (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - Casson, Dame Sybil Thorndike & family, 1929, undated (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - Crawley, I. Sayre, undated (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Day, Ruth Lynda, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - Field, Ben A., undated (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Forbes-Robertson, undated (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Greet, Ben, n.d (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Kennedy, Edith W. Matthison, 1909, undated (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Lytton, L. Rogers, 1908, undated (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Mabie, Hamilton W., undated (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - McLaughlin, Millicent, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Nilsson, Christine, undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Pigott, R.S., undated (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Rees, Alys, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Riggs, Kate Douglas (Wiggin), 1898 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Rignold, George, undated (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Schley, W.S., undated (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Varesi, Gilda, undated (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Vivian, Ruth & Violet, undated (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Von Bulow, Baroness, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 5, Folder 204)